<!-- <ac:layout>
	<ac:layout-section ac:type="single">
		<ac:layout-cell>
		</ac:layout-cell>
	</ac:layout-section>
</ac:layout> -->
<ac:structured-macro ac:name="section">
  <ac:rich-text-body>
    <ac:structured-macro ac:name="column">
      <ac:parameter ac:name="width">60%</ac:parameter>
      <ac:rich-text-body>
            <h2>
				<at:var at:name="spaceHomepageHeading" />
			</h2>
			<p>
				<at:var at:name="spaceDesc" />
			</p>
			<p>
				This is the index page for the Software Architecture Documentation with the english version of the arc42 standard as a template.
			</p>

      <p><b>arc42</b> supports software- and system architects. It is based upon practical experience of many architecture projects of different sizes and domains. It includes feedback of its many users.</p>
      <p><b>arc42</b> contains a template for development, documentation and communication of software architectures.</p>
      <p><b>arc42</b> fits arbitrary technologies and tools.</p>
      <p><b>arc42</b> therefore ensures better software- and system architectures.</p>

        <p>The easiest way for browsing this space is to turn on the sidebar of confluence. You will find the button for it on the lefthand 
        side at the bottom corner of your browser, portrayed as two arrows. Click on it - and the sidebar will show up.</p>

        <p>The sidebar works like any browser tree structure. It shows all the 12 chapters of the ARC42 Template. 
        Click on the arrow to see the subchapters or hide them again.</p>
        
         <h2>Content Overview</h2>
        <p><b>1. Introduction and Goals</b><br/>
          problem, brief definition of task, quality goals, summary of architecturally relevant requirements, 
          especially the non-functional reqs, list of stakeholder.</p>
        <p><b>2. Constraints</b><br/>
         What kind of constraints restrict design decisions?</p>
        <p><b>3. Context</b><br/>
        What's the business and technical context of the system?</p>
        <p><b>4. Solution Ideas and Strategy</b><br/>
        How does the solution work? What are the fundamental solution approaches?</p>
        <p><b>5. Building Block View</b><br/>
        Static structure of system, implementation Blocks.</p>
        <p><b>6. Runtime View</b><br/>
        Cooperation of (instances) of building blocks at runtime, relevant and important interactions.</p>
        <p><b>7. Deployment View</b><br/>
        Deployment: On which hardware will the building blocks be operated? What further information is required to 
        operate the system?</p>
        <p><b>8. Concepts</b><br/>
         Recurring patterns and structures.<br/>
         Business domain models.<br/>
         Crosscutting (technical) concepts.<br/>
         These concepts can often be re-used across systems.</p>
         <p><b>9. Design Decisions</b><br/>
         Important design decisions. </p>
         <p><b>10. Quality Scenarios</b><br/>
         Quality tree with scenarios.</p>
         <p><b>11. Risks</b></p>
         <p><b>12. Glossary</b><br/>
         Important terms.</p>

      </ac:rich-text-body>
    </ac:structured-macro>
    <ac:structured-macro ac:name="column">
      <ac:parameter ac:name="width">40%</ac:parameter>
      
      <ac:rich-text-body>
      
         <ac:image ac:width="150">
                <ri:url ri:value="http://www.arc42.org/index_files/arc42-logo.png"/>
          </ac:image>

        <h2>Table of Contents</h2>
        	<p>
				<ac:macro ac:name="children">
					<ac:parameter ac:name="page"></ac:parameter>
					<ac:parameter ac:name="all">true</ac:parameter>
				</ac:macro>
			</p>

      </ac:rich-text-body>
    </ac:structured-macro>
  </ac:rich-text-body>
    <p>Created with arc42-blueprint v${version}</p>
</ac:structured-macro>

